desktime.com 2014-06-25

# DeskTime - Privacy

## Privacy

**Your privacy is very important to us at DeskTime. If you have any concerns that aren't covered here, please[contact us](https://desktime.com/about/contact/).** Below are the highlights of our policy:

By using our Web site, you agree to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. If we change our privacy policy and procedures, we will post these changes on our website at: <http://desktime.com/about/privacy/> and notify all active accounts of any significant changes to this policy. Your continued use of this site following the posting of any changes to these terms constitutes acceptance of those changes.

  1. DeskTime.com places a high value on personal privacy and therefore **will not share or sell** your personal information collected online with third parties, other than to trusted vendors which include payment processors. Information collected may include your name, email address and billing information, if required for purchases.
  2. **We won't send you spam** mail. We, however, might occasionally send messages about important product news, but you'll always be able to turn this off.
  3. **Other DeskTime users can't see any of your data** or personal information.
  4. DeskTime collects user behavior data including application usage and web site visits. We **do not and never will collect keystrokes, form input, or anything of sensitive nature**. Our records include application name, web site URL, web site title, DeskTime client version, path to the application, start time of use and end time of use. Here’s an example of what the client sends to the server through **secure HTTPS connection** :  

    1. array (
    2. 'now' => '1314172183',
    3. 'version' => '1.0.4289',
    4. 'log' => array (
    5. 0 => array (
    6. 'app' => 'firefox',
    7. 'path' => '\\\Mozilla Firefox\\\firefox.exe',
    8. 'win' => 'jQuery UI - Datepicker Demos & Documentation',
    9. 'url' => 'jqueryui.com',
    10. 'start' => '1314172181'
    11. )
    12. )
    13. );

  5. You can **enable Private Time to pause DeskTime at any time.** If you enable "Private Mode" via the tracker in the system taskbar, DeskTime will stop tracking anything you do on your computer. To enable DeskTime again, just press the "Private Mode" button again.

  6. **You can also delete your account at any time**. Deleting your account deletes all your data from our database.
